双峰
第三季第五集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     小酸奶   一只虾   Silence
翻译     吃冰棒   程程Tara   詹木头
校对     小酸奶
我们刚经过  他的车还停在那里
We just drove by. His car's still there.
搞什么  基恩
What the hell, Gene?
时间轴     没有影子   啾啾啾
他还在里面吗
Is he still inside?
不知道  但是里面的灯亮着
Can't tell, but the lights are on in there.
后期     8T
操  基恩  本来昨天就应该完事了
Fuck, Gene! This job was supposed to be done yesterday.
你是想害死我吗
Are you trying to get me killed?
总监     小酸奶
你想让我们怎么办
What do you want us to do?
我们听你的
We're all over it.
操
Fuck!
她真爱操心
She's a worrier.
是啊
Yeah.
探员
死因
Cause of death...
我花了不少时间  但我觉得是有人把他的头砍了
Took me a while, but I think someone cut this man's head off.
头条来了
Here's the headline.
其实我已经给你们看过"头条"了
Actually, I just gave you the headline.
没错  我周末还是会去讲单口相声
Yeah, I'm still doing stand-up on the weekends.
这个人好几天没吃东西了
This man hadn't eaten for days,
至少没吃过什么食物
at least not any food,
但我在他肚子里找到了这个
but I found this in his stomach.
恕我愚见  我会从妻子入手
Maybe it's just me, but I'd start with the wife.
上面有刻字
It's inscribed.
是的  刻的是
Yes, it says...
"给道吉
"To Dougie,
爱你  珍妮·E"
with love, Janey-E."
现在  吃的来了
And now food is coming.
你还和我一起
You're still with me.
很好
That's good.
帮我叫史蒂文进来一下
Could you send in Steven, please?
先生  你想见我
Sir, you wanted to see me?
没错  我想见你  坐
Yes, I wanted to see you. Sit down.
好吧
Okay.
很好
Great.
不大好
Yeah, well, not great.
你觉得你自己很厉害吗
You think you're some sort of hotshot?
什么
Excuse me?
这是我见过写得最差的简历
This résumé is one of the worst written I've ever seen,
你的表格都没填对
and you didn't even fill out this form properly.
完全不对  没完成
Not even close. It's incomplete.
根本不是懒惰的程度
It's worse than sloppy.
我想见你是想告诉你
I wanted to see you to tell you
如果你想找到工作
that if you ever want to find work anyplace,
你最好表现好一点  做该做的事
then you better get your act together, do things properly,
作为一名未来的员工  表现出一点应有的尊重
and start showing some respect for a possible future employer,
因为就凭这张表  这里永远不会雇你
because based on this shit, you'd never get hired here,
我也绝对不会为你做任何推荐
and I would never recommend you for any work, anyplace.
现在你可以站起来离开这里了
Now, you can get up and get your ass out of here.
真是混蛋
What an asshole.
双峰镇
警局
那可难办了
That's rough.
是啊
Yeah.
你什么时候能拿到那些结果
When do you get those tests back?
杜鲁门警长
Sheriff Truman?
你妻子来了
Your wife is here.
她去你办公室了  你不在那里
She went to your office, and you weren't there.
我没告诉她
I could have told her that.
-等一下  -她现在正在
- Hold on a minute.  - She is now walking
去副警长霍克的办公室
to Deputy Chief Hawk's office,
你就在里面
where you are.
谢谢你  露西
Thank you, Lucy.
多丽丝来了
Doris is coming.
你坚持住  哈里
You hang tough, Harry.
好吧  我明天再来找你
Okay. I'll check in with you tomorrow.
你为什么不在你自己办公室
Why aren't you in your office?
因为我在这里
Because I'm here.
你在嘲笑我吗
You making fun of me?
什么事  多丽丝
What is it, Doris?
德怀特腹泻了
Dwight's got diarrhea.
双胞胎这周末要来
The twins are coming this weekend.
他又爬到最上面的碗橱了
He got in the upper cupboard again.
管道漏水都不能让我喘一口气
And I am not going another day with a leaking pipe.
厨房地板都被淹没了
It soaked the pantry floor,
我们要长黑霉菌了  弗兰克
and we're gonna get that black mold, Frank!
你打给他们了吗
Did you call them?
打了
Yes.
他们很忙
They're very busy.
他们知道管道漏水的事了
They know all about the leaking pipe
保证明晚之前就能修好
and promise to have it fixed by tomorrow night.
那也就是说我还得忍一整天
So I have to go a full day with a leaking pipe?
你知道这会导致什么后果吗
Do you realize what this is gonna cause?
你放了一个桶在下面吗
You have a bucket under it?
没错
Yes!
但桶会满
But it filled up,
然后水又会溢到地板上
and it slopped all over the floor.
我不可能盯着那水桶一天  弗兰克
I can't keep my eye on a bucket all day, Frank.
你能买个大点的桶吗
Can you get a bigger bucket?
所以我是要把钱花在一个
So I can spend money on a bucket
我们以后可能不会再用的水桶上
that we'll probably never use again,
却不能用这钱买
but I can't spend money
我那张超爱的地毯
on that new rug that I really like.
是这个意思吗
Is that it?
这不公平  弗兰克
That is not fair, Frank.
还有我爸爸的车呢
And what about Dad's car?
我是不会
I'm not gonna have him killed
让他被那破车害死的
in that damn death-trap car.
我跟你说过这事了
I told you this.
萨米去看过了
Sammy looked at it,
没什么问题
and it's fine.
什么时候
When?
大概两小时之前吧
About two hours ago.
你怎么不打电话告诉我
Well, I wish you would've called me.
我就可以在家里等着了
I've been just waiting at the house
以防爸爸要搭车去什么地方
in case Dad needed a ride somewhere.
你真是无可救药
You're impossible!
上车  桑尼·吉姆
Go get in the car, Sonny Jim.
听着  我把钱都藏好了
Okay, I hid the money.
我数过
I counted it--
一共有425,000美元
$425,000.
不用担心  它们在很隐秘的地方
Don't worry. It's in our secret place.
现在  你到公司后给他们打个电话  定个时间
Now, when you get to work, call them and set up a time
然后给他们5万美元  行吗
and pay them their 50 grand, okay?
从此我们就付清债务自由了
Then we'll be free and clear.
好了  道吉  你真他妈奇怪
Okay, Dougie, you're acting weird as shit.
别忘了打给他们  好吗
Just don't forget to call them, okay?
以后别再去喝酒赌博了
And no more drinking and gambling.
走吧  你上班快迟到了
Now get going. You'll be late for work.
上班
Work.
你的车
Damn. Your car.
行了  上车  我送你去公司
Okay, get in. I'll drive you.
话说  你的车去哪了
Where is your car, anyway?
上车
In the car!
兰彻·罗莎
内华达州
下车  道吉
Get out of the car, Dougie.
你应该是这几天状态不好
I think you're having one of your episodes.
听我说
Now listen to me.
你要打起精神来
You need to pull yourself together
好好工作
and get to work.
好了快下车
Get out of this car now.
下车上班去
Get out of this car and go to work.
道吉  去上班
Dougie, get to work.
道吉
Dougie!
搞什么
Honestly.
又回来了  道吉
Off in dreamland again, huh, Dougie?
快走  伙计
Get the lead out, pal.
三分钟之后员工会议
Staff meeting starts in three minutes.
玛丽
Mary.
七楼
Seven up.
好
All right.
咖啡
Coffee.
抱歉  道吉  我没有买你那份
Sorry, Dougie. I didn't get one for you.
我都不知道你今天会回来
I didn't even know if you'd be here today.
-咖啡  -好吧
- Coffee. - All right.
你喝弗兰克那杯吧
You can have Frank's.
反正他从来不喝他自己那杯
He never drinks his, anyway,
而且我多买了杯绿茶
and I got an extra green tea.
可能他会喜欢  对吧
Maybe he'll like that, huh?
很他妈好喝对吧  道吉
Damn good joe, huh, Dougie?
-很他妈好喝  -是的
- damn good joe. - Yeah, yeah.
很好喝
It's pretty damn good.
幸运7号保险公司
你好  感谢你能来
Hey, thanks for coming in.
我希望一切顺利
I hope everything's okay.
是的  没问题
Yeah, no problem.
咖啡
Coffee?
你还好吗
You all right?
我不认识他
I don't know him.
道吉
Dougie...
来吧  兄弟
come on, pal.
来这边
Come along.
看看是谁从宾夕法尼亚回来了
Look who's back from Bendersville.
还换了个新发型
With a new haircut.
我帮你收拾了烂摊子  伙计
I covered for your ass, pal.
你欠我个大人情
You owe me big-time for that.
你干什么了
What'd you do?
你在蒸汽浴室里喝酒了吗
Did you go drinking in a steam bath?
好吧
Okay.
早上好
Good morning.
你收到我的信息了吗
Did you get my note?
我没收到你的信息
No, I didn't get your note.
我发给你了
I sent you one.
这话去和你老婆说  达伦
Tell it to your wife, Darren.
菲利
Hey, Phil.
我把你的咖啡给了道吉  抱歉
I gave Dougie your coffee. I'm sorry.
他真的很想喝
He really wanted it.
你要不要喝绿茶拿铁
Do you want this green tea latte?
不要
No.
我想喝那杯
I wa-- I want that.
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧
Okay.
我试试吧
I'll try it.
好了  我们开始吧
All right, let's get started.
坐下  道吉
Sit down, Dougie.
别浪费时间  道吉
Cut the shit, Dougie.
来  来
Come here. Come here.
道吉
Dougie.
坐这  来
Right here. Come on.
托尼  开始吧
Tony, lead us off.
好  这周我收到十六起新的索赔案件
Okay, I've got, uh, 16 new claims this week,
上周有两起
and two claims from last week
已经处理并核实了
have been processed and approved,
所以我们必须理赔
so we have to pay out.
那些都是什么案子
Which ones are those?
比克尔一家的总水管坏了  还有利特菲尔德
The Beakers, who had the broken water main and Littlefield.
法医认为利特菲尔德涉嫌纵火案
Forensics made Littlefield for arson.
根本没有纵火案  布什内尔
There-- there's no arson, Bushnell.
检查员搞清楚并核实了
The inspectors cleared it. It checks out.
没有违法行为
It's legit.
我们必须承付赔偿要求
We have to honor the claim.
他在说谎
He's lying.
你说什么
What'd you say?
What did you say?
你说我是骗子吗  道吉
Are you calling me a liar, Dougie?
你凭什么说我是骗子
Where the hell do you get off calling me a liar?
你这话什么意思  道吉
What do you mean by that, Dougie?
结束后  你来我办公室一趟
I want you in my office as soon as we're finished here.
正如我所说的
So, like I was saying,
利特菲尔德没有违法行为
Littlefield's legit.
我可以继续吗
May I continue?
如果你没意见的话  道吉
Is that okay with you, Dougie?
我的朋友
My friend?
把门关上
Close the door behind you...
出去再关上
...on your way out.
道吉  你胆子不小啊
Dougie, where do you get the stones
说我最好的探员是骗子
to call my best agent a liar?
探员
Agent.
他一周内破的案子
He closes more cases in a week
比你一个月破的还多
than you do in a month.
探员
Agent.
这是严重的问题  道吉  这可不是儿戏
This is serious, Dougie. This is no game.
儿戏
Game.
好吧  道吉  我们来玩个游戏
Okay, Dougie, we'll play a game.
课外游戏
It's a homework game,
因为你前两天没去学校
since you missed the last two days of school,
聪明人
smart guy.
我要你今晚把这些案件卷宗带回家
I want you to take these case files home with you tonight.
每一件案子都要做一个全面的分析
I need a full assessment on each case.
明天你带回来的报告
And what you come back with tomorrow
可和你在这家公司的未来
will have a whole hell of a lot to do
息息相关
with your future at this company.
案件卷宗
Case files.
男厕锁住了吗
Is the men's room locked?
来  我帮你偷溜进女厕
Come on, I'll sneak you in the ladies'.
来
Come on.
我在想
You know, I was thinking...
也许我现在会让你亲亲我  帅哥
maybe I'll let you kiss me now, handsome.
进去吧
Okay, go ahead.
我会帮你放哨的
I'll keep watch.
银色野马赌场
我是
Yes?
我现在告诉他
I'll tell him now.
他们正上来这里
They're on their way up.
一连中三十次头奖
Thirty jackpots in a row.
我们一年内都没支出过这么多次
We haven't paid out that many in a year.
让他转身
Turn him around.
监视器上那个人赢了多少钱
How much did that man there on the television win?
四十二万五千美金
$425,000.
四十二万五...
Four hundred twenty f--
你想告诉我们你和这事没关系吗
And you're trying to tell us that you weren't in on this?
再说一次  那人赢了多少钱
How much did that man win, again?
四十二万五千美金
$425,000.
你被炒鱿鱼了
You're fucking fired.
把他带走
Get him out of here.
离开这个小镇
Leave town.
永远不要回来
Don't ever come back.
你
You.
他的职位归你了
You got his job.
如果这个人再来这里  告诉我们
You let us know if this man ever comes in here again.
滚开  小屁孩  给我滚开
Fuck off, kid! Get the fuck out of here!
操
Fuck!
都搞定了  杰德
All done, Jade.
你搞了个华盛顿州的家伙
Hey, you got a john in the state of Washington?
什么
What?
在你车里找到了这把酒店钥匙
Found this hotel key in your car.
大北方酒店
华盛顿州双峰镇  315号房
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
环境卫生  价格合理
等我一会儿  克里斯
Give me a second, Chris.
特德  面包在这里
Toad, bread's here.
你好  特德
Hey, Toad.
你好啊  贝基
Hiya, Becky.
-谢谢  -谢谢你  亲爱的
- Thank you. - Thank you, dear.
你好
Hi.
怎么了
What's up?
我受不了了
I can't stand this.
我需要更多钱
I need some more money.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
他在找工作
He's looking for work.
这数目可不小
That's a lot.
他会找到工作的
He will find a job.
-亲爱的  我可以给你这么多  -好吧
- Honey, I can give you this. - Okay.
-但我只有这些了  -谢谢  我爱你
- But this is all I got. - Thanks. I love you.
我也爱你  贝基
I love you, too, Becky.
雪莉  这两个星期
Shelly, this is the third time
她已经找你要了三次钱了
she's asked you for money in two weeks.
我知道
I know.
如果现在不帮她
If you don't help her now,
之后就更难帮了
it's gonna get a lot harder to help her later.
我们都很明白  对吗
We both know that tune, don't we?
要到了多少钱
How much money did we get?
72块
$72.
高兴点  我都准备好了
Hey, cheer up. I'm good for it.
我会还给她的
I'll pay her back.
她们在看我们
They're watching us.
我要走了
I'm gonna roll.
吻我
Kiss me.
现在我要带我的女友去吃晚餐
And now I'm gonna take my girl out to dinner.
我给你留了一点
Hey, I saved some for you.
想尝一尝吗
Want a taste?
你今天全都带出来了吗
Did you take all of that today?
是啊
Yeah.
怎么了
Why?
为什么不
Why wouldn't I?
这是为面试准备的  你知道我容易紧张
For my interviews. You know how nervous I get.
别生气了
Come on.
再说  我今天还得到了一些很棒的反馈呢
Besides, I got some great fucking feedback today.
我晚饭的时候再跟你说
I'll tell you all about it at dinner.
在那之前  我要告诉你...
And in between, I'll tell you...
我有多爱你
how much I love you,
我要告诉你  你有多美
and I'll tell you how beautiful you are,
我还要告诉你
and I'll tell you
你有多性感
how sexy you are,
这奶子  有多大
and those tits, how majestic they are,
还有这屁股  饶了我吧
and that ass-- give me a break,
我还要给你买点面包
and I'll get you some bread.
为什么
Why?
因为我听说你揉了一天的面包了
Because I heard you've been kneading it all day.
我爱你吻我时
I love how your eyes close
闭着眼睛的样子
whenever you kiss me.
我爱我不在你身边时
And when I'm away from you,
你想我的样子
I love how you miss me.
-到了  伙计  -借过
- Okay, all right, buddy. - Excuse us.
-让一下  -快点  道吉  让开
- Come on. - Come on, Dougie, move!
-我们已经到了  -喂
- We have arrived. - Hello?
-快走啊  -道吉  快走啊
- Come on! - Dougie, come on.
-天啊  -别挡道
- Jeez! - Get out of the way.
双峰镇警察局
霍克
Hawk?
你有找到印第安人吗
Have you found any Indians?
任何地方
Anywhere?
我还没看到任何印第安人
I-I haven't found any Indians.
没有  安迪
No, Andy.
七点了
It's seven o'clock.
你知道自由在哪吗
Do you know where your freedom is?
A号广播电台
Coming to you live
为您带来现场直播
and electrified from studio A,
来自美国兴都库什山的
high atop the escarpments of White Tail Peak,
屋脊
the roof-- ruff, ruff--
白尾峰峭壁之巅的声音
of the American Hindu Kush,
这里是安普博士
this is Dr. Amp
唱响独立的颂歌
doing the vamp for liberty,
爬上正义的巅峰
climbing the ramp to justice,
点亮自由的灯火
and lighting the lamp of freedom.
那么
So...
你们今天晚上都在想些什么呢
what's on your mind tonight?
你知道我会讲我在想什么
I mean, you know I'm gonna tell you what's on mine.
我们正在陷入深深的泥潭
We're sinking down deep in the mud,
那帮混蛋又来了
and the fucks are at it again!
还是那个全球企业的阴谋
The same vast global corporate conspiracy.
时代不同而已
Different day.
你没有宇宙手电筒就看不到这些
You can't see it without a cosmic flashlight.
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
我有一个
I've got one.
对
Oh, yeah.
它的光芒能够穿透
And its beam, it penetrates
无知的火山岩
the igneous rock of ignorance.
它把那石头翻开
It flips that rock over,
就把一切大白于天下
and there they are, exposed,
真相躲闪着  扭动着
wriggling, squirming,
像蛆一样爬行
crawling on their bellies like foul maggots,
疯狂地想要回到它们渴望的
frantically racing back to the cover of darkness
黑暗的角落中
that they so crave.
我们来找你了
We're coming for you.
是的  我们来找你了
Yeah, we're coming for you.
让我们看看它们今天又在酝酿些什么
Let's just see what they're cooking up today.
我知道我会酝酿什么
I know what I'll be cooking up.
看清楚那些原材料
Know the ingredients.
看看包装盒上都写了什么
Just read what's on the box.
事实上  看清字里行间的隐藏信息
In fact, read between the lines.
那些烤华夫饼里都藏着什么
What's lurking in that-- that toaster waffle,
还有那些松糕
those muffins...
那些冷冻儿童小零食
...that frozen children's treat?
毒药
Poison!
致命的毒药
Deadly poisons.
里面就是这些
That's what's there.
知道什么在等着你吗
And what's waiting for you?
癌症
Cancer!
白血病
Leukemia!
自体免疫性疾病
Autoimmune disorders!
肺栓塞
Pulmonary embolism!
肉疣
Warts!
牛皮鲜  湿疹
Psoriasis, eczema!
心脏骤停
Cardiac arrest!
警察在我们需要的时候都到哪去了
Where are the cops when we need them?
厌食症
Anorexia,
身体表象那些屁话
body-image bullshit,
微生物毒素  细菌毒素
microbial toxins, bacterial toxins,
环境毒素
environmental toxins!
我们的空气  水  地球
Our air, our water, our earth.
我们的土壤
The very soil itself!
食物
Our food!
我们的身体  都被毒害了
Our bodies poisoned!
毒害了
Poisoned!
这是
That's...
黑果汁
huckleberry extract
加上干净煮沸过的水
in clean, boiled water
来自白尾峰上
from the pure, artesian springs
纯净的自流泉
of White Tail Peak.
对
Yeah.
让亚马逊的巴西莓去死吧
Fuck that acai berry shit from the Amazon.
用皮特·西格的不朽名言来说
In the immortal words of Pete Seeger,
如果我有一把锤子
if I had a hammer...
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
我真有把锤子
I've got a hammer.
你必须看到
You must see,
听到  理解  并行动
hear, understand, and act.
立刻行动起来
Act now.
朋友们  我们都生活在泥潭里
Friends, we all live in the mud.
在一摊屎里
In the shit!
快把自己从屎里铲出来
Shovel your way out of the shit.
用这把亮闪闪的金铲子
This is your shiny, gold shovel.
双层漆  质量保证
Two coats, guaranteed.
帮你从屎里脱身
Shovel your way out of the shit
来迎接真理
and into the truth.
从屎坑脱身  只要二十九块九九
Dig yourself out of the shit--$29.99.
没错
That's right.
只要二十九块九九  不包邮
Only $29.99 plus shipping.
安普博士牌
金色屎铲
概不退换
Accept no substitute.
欲购从速
Get yours now.
五角大楼  阿灵顿  弗吉尼亚州
你可以进去了
You can go in now.
我们又检测到一次数据访问
We got another database hit
访问的是加兰德·布里格斯少校的文件
on prints for Major Garland Briggs.
加兰德·布里格斯少校
Major Garland Briggs.
好吧
All right.
这是第几次了
And how many is that?
第十六次
This would be the 16th time.
这刚多久  二十五年里出了十六次
Sixteen hits in, what, 25 years?
这次的是哪里
And where'd this one come from?
警局
Police.
鹿角镇  南达科他州
Buckhorn, South Dakota.
估计这次去也还是白费力气
Another wild-goose chase, I bet,
但还是得去调查一下
but we got to check it out.
去过南达科他吗  辛迪
You ever been to South Dakota, Cindy?
听说现在去正是好时候
I hear it's lovely this time of year.
记好了  如果这次是真的的话...
And remember, if this is real--
但应该不会是...
but it won't be--
不过要是动真格的话
but if it's real,
我们必须要向联调局汇报
we have to alert the FBI.
我去订机票
I'm booking the flight.
订头等舱  辛迪
First class, Cindy.
没问题
Yeah, right.
禁止吸烟
请你别再抽了
I have to ask you to stop smoking.
把烟灭了
Put that cigarette out.
你能怎样
Make me.
我来处理吧
I'll take care of this.
就让他别在这抽烟了
Just make sure he stops smoking in here.
明白了
Okay?
给我来支烟
Give me a smoke.
整包都拿走吧
Keep the whole pack.
谢了  伙计
Thanks, buddy.
能借个火吗
Hey, can I have a light?
过来
Come here.
坐下
Sit down.
怎么了
Hey what?
你叫什么
Hey, what's your name?
-夏洛特  -是吗
- Charlotte. - Yeah?
想上我吗  夏洛特
You want to fuck me, Charlotte?
想来上我吗
You want to fuck?
不  快放手
No. No, stop it.
快放开她
Hey, leave her alone.
一群抽烟的小骚货
Little fucking smoking babies.
看得我想笑
Makes me laugh.
我要一边笑一边干你  贱货
I'm gonna laugh when I fuck you, bitch!
就打一个电话
One phone call.
谢谢你  墨菲典狱长
Thank you, Warden Murphy.
在录着吗
Are we recording?
都录下来了
Recording everything.
既然大家都到齐了
Now that everyone's here,
我就要打电话了
I will make my phone call.
该打给谁呢
Now, who should I call?
打给草莓先生吗
Should I call Mr. Strawberry?
怎么回事
What the hell?
不  还是不打给草莓先生了
No, I don't think I'll call Mr. Strawberry.
我觉得他不会接的
I don't think he's taking calls.
我知道了
I know.
我知道该打给谁了
I know who to call.
怎么回事
What the hell?
他怎么弄的  他怎么弄的
How is he doing this? How is he doing this?
他打了个电话吗  拨的什么号码
Did he make a call? What number did he dial?
奶牛跳过了月亮
The cow jumped over the moon.
他刚刚干了什么
What did this guy just do?
布利诺斯艾利斯  阿根廷
先生
Sir?
不能在这里瞎晃  先生
There's no loitering here, sir.
快走吧  伙计
Move it along, champ.